{
    "question": "Lanjutan jawaban dari \"in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens already live in cities, urbanization is spread evenly, and population growth\" pilihan nya    a. has slowed\r\nb. would slow\r\nc. slowed\r\nd. had slowed\r\ne. will slow\r\n(simple future tense)",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "d. in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens al already live in cities. urbanization is spread evenly. and population growth <u>had slowed</u>. <br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "bisa saja isinya yang\u00a0<br>b. would slow, karena future pasti akan menggunakan will dan would adalah bentuk kedua dari modals tsb",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-kalimat-verbal-dalam-bahasa-inggris-610",
            "question": "5\u00a0kalimat verbal dalam\u00a0bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "We play football every morning<br>I go to the market every sunday<br>She plays soccer with Ella<br>He goes to the library<br>She buys some books in the store<br>Semoga Membantu<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858",
            "question": "Whats is the problem from the story \"Snow Bride\"",
            "attachments": [
                "question-attachments/whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858-1.docx"
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Carilah kata-kata yang terdengar janggal dan aneh... :)Mandiri lebih baik.<br>Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-beri-penjelasan-tentang-word-order-dengan-rinci-844",
            "question": "Tolong Beri Penjelasan Tentang Word Order\u00a0Dengan Rinci",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Word order atau tata urut kata merupakan cara untuk\nmenyusun kata \u2013 kata dalam urutan atau susunan yang tepat dan benar. </span>\n\n<br><br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Word order adalah susunan kata-kata dalam kalimat, artinya bahwa cara kita menempatkan setiap kata itu haruslah sesuai dengan fungsinya dalam membentuk suatu kalimat. Caranya dengan mengetahui dan menghafal rumus atau pola baku.<br>Contoh:<br>&#039;&#039; Sebuah mobil mewah baru buatan Amerika Serikat &#039;&#039; diterjemahkan menjadi \" A new American car \".<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-artinya-shawty-182",
            "question": "Apa artinya shawty ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "shawty itu bahasa slang-nya bhs inggris yang artinya cantik,menarik.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "minta-tolong-kasi-contoh-percakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pernya-886",
            "question": "Minta tolong kasi contoh percakapan bahasa inggris tentang pernyataan setuju dan tidak setuju",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Class Vacation<br><br><span>Yoga\t: So, class. Now we are going to deliberate our concern about where we are going to head for our class vacation. So, who comes up with the idea first?<br>Habibi\t: I will vote for Anyer Beach. Anyer Beach is one of the nearest beaches we can visit.<br>Yoga\t: So, class. Is there anyone who disagrees with Anyer Beach?<br>Jenny\t: Um, I am not sure about that. Last vacation our class had gone to Anyer Beach. I think we should see other options.<br>Habibi\t: Oh yeah! You\u2019re right, I forgot about that.<br>Jefri\t: Well, I\u2019m suggesting Kebun Raya Bogor<br>Kania\t: I agree with you, Jefri. I have never been there myself.<br>Geri\t: Me too, I am with you, Kania. Seeing great trees and plants must be exciting. Kebun Raya Bogor is like a great jungle in the middle of town.<br>Sarah\t: I\u2019m sorry guys. I think I will disagree with that. It\u2019s rainy season now. And as you know, Kebun Raya Bogor is located in Bogor which is the city of rain. And seeing the intensity of rainfall throughout Indonesia lately, I think we might not be able to explore the whole Kebun Raya Bogor due to the rain.<br>Tio\t: I think what Sarah said is right. Kebun Raya Bogor is not the best place to visit during this heavy rainy season<br>Yoga\t: Well, are there any other options?<br>Fauzi\t: How about Bali?<br>Habibi\t: No way! I don\u2019t have enough money to go to Bali<br>Sarah\t: Habibi is right, Fauzi. It\u2019s really costly to pick Bali as an option.<br>Yoga\t: Okay, class. To save the time, now let\u2019s just write your idea into a piece of paper and we will deliberate in the next occasion. Thank you.<br><br>contoh yang lebih simple lagi :)<br><br></span>A : hi, good morning B<br>B : morning A, how are you??<br>A : i&#039;m fine thank&#039;s<br>B : are you agree if i break up with C??<br>A : no, i don&#039;t<br>B : why??<br>A : I&#039;m not agree if you break up with C, because she more Love you then anyone, bro don&#039;t break up with her, and maybe sometime you can&#039;t find girl like C anymore, so don&#039;t break up with her<br>B : uhh, okay broooo, thank&#039;s for that<br><span>A : your welcome dude....<br></span><br>sekian dari saya :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Lin :I can&#039;t help to hold on any longer.<br>Sara : Oh why?<br>Lin : I think he truly never cares about me. He keeps talking about his ex-girl friend and it hurts me. He doesn&#039;t love me anymore!<br>Sara : <em>I don&#039;t think so</em>, Lin! Jey does love you so much. I know it. You&#039;re everything to him. Probably he did that just want to know how your response is. He wants to know whether you love him as he loves you. Ask him yourself and keep positive thinking. Don&#039;t ever let him go because of your emotion.<br>Lin : <em><strong>I think you&#039;re right</strong></em>. It might be better to talk to him directly. Thanks, Sara.<br>Sara : you are very welcome.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggris-dia-mengernyitkan-alisnya-547",
            "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "did-he-has-a-bad-seat-203",
            "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}